potholesinmyblog.com 2011-04-29

# MMN Publisher Privacy Policy - MOG Music Network

Privacy Policy for Consumers  
July 2010 

Advertisers are committed to privacy and to giving you choice in the advertising that you view. This privacy policy explains the types of data collected, how long it’s used, and how long it’s kept. 

What Advertiser’s DON’T Collect: Advertisers do not collect any personally identifiable information. This is information that would allow someone to know both your name and contact or financial information such as a telephone number, email address, complete street address, or credit card number. 

About Children: Children are people too. Advertisers don’t collect children’s (or anyone else’s) personal information. 

What do Advertisers Collect? To deliver the most relevant advertising to you, Advertisers collect anonymous data when you visit our site. That data may include the URL of the site or page you visited, your IP address (which provides some level of geographic detail more general than zip codes), the time of day, and the category of ads that were presented to you or that you interacted with. Advertisers may collect information regarding the interaction (for example, pausing or rewinding a video advertisement). Advertisers may collect information that tells Advertisers what led you to the site (referring URL or search query). This information is stored on the Advertiser’s servers with a random numeric id – and Advertiser’s store that numeric ID, encrypted, in your browser as a cookie. Collectively, Advertiser’s refer to all of this information as “cookie targeting data”. None of this information can be used to personally identify you. 

What Advertisers do with the data collected: Using the cookie targeting data, Advertisers can specify characteristics shared by groups of users that may be desired for an advertising campaign (we only target ads against aggregated information). Advertisers can also use cookie targeting data to affect the number of times you are presented with a particular ad or set of ads within a period of time (so-called “frequency-capping”). For example, a pet food producer would like to present its product to consumers who live in the San Francisco Bay Area and are possibly interested, based on browsing history, in pets. If Advertisers determine that the Advertiser’s cookie on your browser may be associated with viewing pet-related website and with an IP address in the San Francisco Bay Area, you may be more likely to be presented with an advertisement from that producer. And Advertisers determine otherwise, you may be less likely to be presented with an advertisement from that producer. Advertisers do not have a mechanism for advertisers to know the personal identity of the person receiving the targeted advertisements. Advertisers may share with third parties aggregated, non-personally identifiable information, such as the number of users who visit a publisher site or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. This information does not identify you individually. The example of an Advertiser’s use of cookie targeting information is not comprehensive. In general, Advertisers will use cookie targeted data to facilitate the requirements of advertisers so long as such use does not personally identify you. 

How long do Advertisers keep the Data? Advertisers store cookie targeting data for as long as 60 days. Certain data, such as the category of ads on specific sites and pages are retained, in aggregate, to inform Advertisers decision engine for serving the most relevant ads to any consumer on a non-targeted basis. Frequency-capping cookie data is retained on the consumer’s browser for as long as specified in specific campaign requirements. Advertiser’s servers do not store frequency-capping cookie data. 

FURTHER INFORMATION 

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about the collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact MMN via mmn-AT-mog-dot-com.
